Create a tunnel that's accessible on vscode.dev from anywhere. Run `code tunnel --help` for more usage info

Usage: code-tunnel.exe tunnel [OPTIONS] [COMMAND]

Commands:
  prune       Delete all servers which are currently not running
  kill        Stops any running tunnel on the system
  restart     Restarts any running tunnel on the system
  status      Gets whether there is a tunnel running on the current machine
  rename      Rename the name of this machine associated with port forwarding service
  unregister  Remove this machine's association with the port forwarding service
  user        
  service     (Preview) Manages the tunnel when installed as a system service,
  help        Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)

Options:
      --install-extension <INSTALL_EXTENSION>
          Requests that extensions be preloaded and installed on connecting servers
      --server-data-dir <SERVER_DATA_DIR>
          Specifies the directory that server data is kept in
      --extensions-dir <EXTENSIONS_DIR>
          Set the root path for extensions
      --reconnection-grace-time <RECONNECTION_GRACE_TIME>
          Reconnection grace time in seconds. Defaults to 10800 (3 hours)
  -h, --help
          Print help

ADVANCED OPTIONS:
      --random-name                  Randomly name machine for port forwarding service
      --no-sleep                     Prevents the machine going to sleep while this command runs
      --name <NAME>                  Sets the machine name for port forwarding service
      --accept-server-license-terms  If set, the user accepts the server license terms and the server will be started without a user prompt

GLOBAL OPTIONS:
      --cli-data-dir <CLI_DATA_DIR>  Directory where CLI metadata should be stored [env: VSCODE_CLI_DATA_DIR=]
      --verbose                      Print verbose output (implies --wait)
      --log <level>                  Log level to use [possible values: trace, debug, info, warn, error, critical, off]
